<resources>
    <string name="nav_open">Open</string>
    <string name="nav_close">Close</string>
    <string name="pPeep">P-PEEP</string>
    <string name="app_name">PpeepAPP</string>

    <string name="log_in_text"><u>Log In Here</u></string>
    <string name="termsCondition"><u>Terms &amp;Conditions</u></string>
    <string name="sign_up_text"><u>Create One</u></string>


    <string name="termsConditionText">
    1. INTRODUCTORY
    Important – please read these terms carefully. By using this Service, you agree that you have read, understood, accepted and agreed with the Terms and Conditions, and the conditions stated in the Driver’s Code of Conduct. You further agree to the representations made by yourself below. If you do not agree to or fall within the Terms and Conditions of the Service (as defined below) and wish to discontinue using the Service, please do not continue using this Application or Service. The terms and conditions stated herein (collectively, the “Terms and Conditions” or this “Agreement”) constitute a legal agreement between you and Pathao Ltd.(the “Company”).

    In order to use the Service (each as defined below) you must agree to the Terms and Conditions that are set out below. By using the mobile application supplied to you by the Company (the “Application”), and downloading, installing or using any associated software supplied by the Company (the “Software”) which overall purpose is to enable the Service (each as defined below), you hereby expressly acknowledge and agree to be bound by the Terms and Conditions, and any future amendments and additions to this Terms and Conditions as published from time to time at Pathao or through the Application.

    2. SERVICES
    The Company offers information, method and platform for transportation providers, drivers and vehicle operators to schedule, obtain and establish contact with Passengers or Customers, but does not and does not intend to provide transportation services or act in any way as a taxi operator, transportation carrier or provider, and has no responsibility or liability for any transportation services provided to Passengers or Customers by you.

    The Company reserves the right to modify, vary or change the terms and conditions of this Agreement or its policies relating to the Service at any time as it deems fit. Such modifications, variations or changes to the Terms and Conditions policies relating to the Service shall be effective upon the posting of an updated version at Pathao. You agree that it shall be your responsibility to review this Agreement regularly whereupon the continued use of the Service after any such changes, whether or not reviewed by you, shall constitute your consent and acceptance to such changes.

    3. NOT A TRANSPORTATION PROVIDER
    THE COMPANY IS A TECHNOLOGY COMPANY THAT DOES NOT PROVIDE OR ENGAGE IN TRANSPORTATION SERVICES AND THE COMPANY IS NOT A TRANSPORTATION PROVIDER. THE SOFTWARE AND THE APPLICATION ARE INTENDED TO BE USED FOR FACILITATING YOU (AS A TRANSPORTATION PROVIDER) TO OFFER YOUR TRANSPORTATION SERVICES TO YOUR PASSENGER OR CUSTOMER. THE COMPANY IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR THE ACTS AND/OR OMISSIONS WITH REGARD TO ANY SERVICES YOU PROVIDED TO YOUR PASSENGERS, AND FOR ANY ILLEGAL ACTION COMMITTED BY YOU. YOU SHALL, AT ALL TIME, NOT CLAIM OR CAUSE ANY PERSON TO MISUNDERSTAND THAT YOU ARE THE AGENT, EMPLOYEE OR STAFF OF THE COMPANY, AND THE SERVICES PROVIDED BY YOU IS NOT, IN ANYWAY, BE DEEMED AS SERVICES OF THE COMPANY.

    YOU ARE FORBIDDEN FROM PROMOTING COMPETITORS APPLICATIONS, GIVING OUT COUPONS AND SUGGESTING ANY OTHER FORM OF DISCOUNTS TO THE PASSENGERS OR CUSTOMERS.
</string>
</resources>